export const stadiums = [
  {
    id: 1,
    category: "Stadiums",
    question: "Which stadium has the highest seating capacity in the world?",
    options: ["Camp Nou", "Wembley", "Rungrado May Day", "Azteca"],
    answer: "Rungrado May Day",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    category: "Stadiums",
    question: "Which stadium is home to FC Barcelona?",
    options: ["Wanda", "Camp Nou", "Bernabéu", "Allianz"],
    answer: "Camp Nou",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    category: "Stadiums",
    question: "Where is Wembley Stadium located?",
    options: ["Paris", "London", "Rome", "Madrid"],
    answer: "London",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    category: "Stadiums",
    question: "Which stadium hosted the 2014 World Cup final?",
    options: ["Allianz Arena", "Maracanã", "Azteca", "Camp Nou"],
    answer: "Maracanã",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    category: "Stadiums",
    question: "Which Italian stadium is home to AC Milan and Inter?",
    options: [
      "Stadio Olimpico",
      "San Siro",
      "Juventus Stadium",
      "Atleti Azzurri",
    ],
    answer: "San Siro",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    category: "Stadiums",
    question: "Which stadium is known as 'The Theatre of Dreams'?",
    options: ["Anfield", "Old Trafford", "Etihad", "Stamford Bridge"],
    answer: "Old Trafford",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    category: "Stadiums",
    question: "Which stadium hosted the 2010 World Cup final?",
    options: ["Soccer City", "Moses Mabhida", "Cape Town", "Ellis Park"],
    answer: "Soccer City",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    category: "Stadiums",
    question: "Which stadium is home to Bayern Munich?",
    options: [
      "Allianz Arena",
      "Signal Iduna Park",
      "Olympiastadion",
      "Red Bull Arena",
    ],
    answer: "Allianz Arena",
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    category: "Stadiums",
    question: "Which club plays at Signal Iduna Park?",
    options: ["Bayern", "Dortmund", "Leipzig", "Hamburg"],
    answer: "Dortmund",
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    category: "Stadiums",
    question: "Which stadium is home to Real Madrid?",
    options: ["Camp Nou", "Metropolitano", "Bernabéu", "Riazor"],
    answer: "Bernabéu",
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    category: "Stadiums",
    question: "Which stadium has a famous 'Yellow Wall'?",
    options: [
      "Allianz Arena",
      "San Siro",
      "Signal Iduna Park",
      "Parc des Princes",
    ],
    answer: "Signal Iduna Park",
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    category: "Stadiums",
    question: "Which stadium is home to Chelsea?",
    options: ["Stamford Bridge", "Craven Cottage", "Emirates", "Etihad"],
    answer: "Stamford Bridge",
  },
  {
    id: 13,
    category: "Stadiums",
    question: "Which stadium hosted the Euro 2016 final?",
    options: [
      "Parc des Princes",
      "Stade de France",
      "Velodrome",
      "Allianz Riviera",
    ],
    answer: "Stade de France",
  },
  {
    id: 14,
    category: "Stadiums",
    question: "Which Brazilian stadium hosted the 1950 World Cup final?",
    options: ["Maracanã", "Arena Corinthians", "Beira-Rio", "Mineirão"],
    answer: "Maracanã",
  },
  {
    id: 15,
    category: "Stadiums",
    question: "Which stadium is home to Arsenal?",
    options: ["Highbury", "Emirates", "White Hart Lane", "Craven Cottage"],
    answer: "Emirates",
  },
  {
    id: 16,
    category: "Stadiums",
    question: "Which U.S. stadium hosted Copa America Centenario final?",
    options: [
      "Rose Bowl",
      "MetLife Stadium",
      "Levi's Stadium",
      "Mercedes-Benz Stadium",
    ],
    answer: "MetLife Stadium",
  },
  {
    id: 17,
    category: "Stadiums",
    question: "Which stadium is home to PSG?",
    options: [
      "Parc des Princes",
      "Stade de France",
      "Groupama Stadium",
      "Velodrome",
    ],
    answer: "Parc des Princes",
  },
  {
    id: 18,
    category: "Stadiums",
    question: "Which stadium hosted the 1994 World Cup final?",
    options: [
      "Rose Bowl",
      "Giants Stadium",
      "Cotton Bowl",
      "Orlando Citrus Bowl",
    ],
    answer: "Rose Bowl",
  },
  {
    id: 19,
    category: "Stadiums",
    question: "Which stadium is the home of Liverpool FC?",
    options: ["Anfield", "Goodison Park", "Old Trafford", "Etihad"],
    answer: "Anfield",
  },
  {
    id: 20,
    category: "Stadiums",
    question: "Which stadium hosted the Euro 2020 final?",
    options: ["Allianz Arena", "Wembley Stadium", "Stadio Olimpico", "Parken"],
    answer: "Wembley Stadium",
  },
];
